<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linux on Dunkelheit</title>
    <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/tags/linux.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in linux on Dunkelheit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dunkelheit.biz/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stop Bloating Your Shell</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/stop-bloating-your-shell.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/stop-bloating-your-shell.html</guid>
      <description>Probably my favourite part of using Linux is that I can customise my eperience.
The customisation options for some of the fundamental tools I use are endless and they are customisable by design. I have probably spent more time customising, modifying and tweaking my shell configurations than any other piece of software on my system.
For this article I will be using zsh as the example shell unless stated otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Dont Care If You Use Linux</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/i-dont-care-if-you-use-linux.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 19:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/i-dont-care-if-you-use-linux.html</guid>
      <description>You may have seen my previous post about Free (as in freedom) software and came to the conclusion that I want to &amp;ldquo;convert&amp;rdquo; normies to using Linux. This is not the case.
I do not care if you use Linux or not, I do not care what distro you use either. Whatever works for you, works for you and that&amp;rsquo;s great.
The reason I recommend that you use a Linux based OS is not that I personally gain from you doing so but that you will gain from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free As In Freedom</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/free-as-in-freedom.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/free-as-in-freedom.html</guid>
      <description>Libre, not gratis.
I won&amp;rsquo;t go into the specifics of Free Software in this article, if you would like to know more check the references at the bottom of the page.
Freedom is non-negotiable Your freedom as a user is the most important aspect of the software that you use.
A common phrase found online regarding services such as search engines and email service providers goes something like &amp;ldquo;if it&amp;rsquo;s free then you are the product&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
