<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>software on Dunkelheit</title>
    <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/tags/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in software on Dunkelheit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 17:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dunkelheit.biz/tags/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who Cares About Twitter?</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/who-cares-about-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/who-cares-about-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Apparently it&amp;rsquo;s a big deal that Elon Musk bought Twitter. Everyone seems to be competing for the worst take regarding it. Which means it must be the Current Thing™️.
The true based and red pilled position is as always &amp;ldquo;who cares?&amp;rdquo;
Twitter sucks, it always sucked, it will continue to suck.
Elon Musk wants to &amp;ldquo;verify all humans&amp;rdquo;, this effectively means KYCAML for Twitter. Apparently his reasoning for buying Twitter is to secure free speech online or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encrypting an External Storage Device</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/encrypting-an-external-storage-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 09:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/encrypting-an-external-storage-device/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to keep backups of important data, it&amp;rsquo;s an even better idea to make sure only you can access them.
This is a guide on how to encrypt an external storage device for use on a Linux system.
Storage Devices This guide should be relatively universal for most external storage devices.
For this example I am assuming you know what kind of storage device is best for your use case and that you are using a NEW device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating QR Codes for Crypto</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/generating-qr-codes-for-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/generating-qr-codes-for-crypto/</guid>
      <description>If you run a blog or a website or have any kind of online presence then you should be accepting crypto donations.
I will not explain why you should accept crypto here because this article exists. Please read it.
Crypto Addresses You don&amp;rsquo;t need to use third party platforms to do this.
All you need is your address and you are good to go. In this example I will be assuming that you have custody of your crypto wallet(s) and don&amp;rsquo;t use fiat-crypto™️ platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Bloating Your Shell</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/stop-bloating-your-shell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/stop-bloating-your-shell/</guid>
      <description>Probably my favourite part of using Linux is that I can customise my experience.
The customisation options for some of the fundamental tools I use are endless and they are customisable by design. I have probably spent more time customising, modifying and tweaking my shell configurations than any other piece of software on my system.
For this article I will be using zsh as the example shell unless stated otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Emacs Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/the-emacs-rabbit-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/the-emacs-rabbit-hole/</guid>
      <description>I have been using Emacs as my text editor for about a year now. I still have no idea what I am doing but at least I know why.
Cosy and Powerful The Emacs client is very lightweight and it can be self-extended whilst running by using Elisp. I am not quite sure how it works as Elisp is too far down the rabbit hole and I haven&amp;rsquo;t been there yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Dont Care If You Use Linux</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/i-dont-care-if-you-use-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 19:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/i-dont-care-if-you-use-linux/</guid>
      <description>You may have seen my previous post about Free (as in freedom) software and came to the conclusion that I want to &amp;ldquo;convert&amp;rdquo; normies to using Linux. This is not the case.
I do not care if you use Linux or not, I do not care what distro you use either. Whatever works for you, works for you and that&amp;rsquo;s great.
The reason I recommend that you use a Linux based OS is not that I personally gain from you doing so but that you will gain from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free As In Freedom</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/free-as-in-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/free-as-in-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Libre, not gratis.
I won&amp;rsquo;t go into the specifics of Free Software in this article, if you would like to know more check the references at the bottom of the page.
Freedom is non-negotiable Your freedom as a user is the most important aspect of the software that you use.
A common phrase found online regarding services such as search engines and email service providers goes something like &amp;ldquo;if it&amp;rsquo;s free then you are the product&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSS is Based!</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/rss-is-based/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 08:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/rss-is-based/</guid>
      <description>I recently started using Newsboat for RSS.
Getting a proper RSS setup has been on my &amp;ldquo;cosy setup&amp;rdquo; checklist for a while. It didn&amp;rsquo;t take much time at all to get it working either.
I previously just used browser plug-ins for this however this approach is terrible in practice.
Now that I have a proper setup using Newsboat I can truly appreciate RSS feeds and I would recommend using them to anyone that wants to keep up to date with things without engaging with social media.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
