<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>updates on Dunkelheit</title>
    <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/tags/updates.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in updates on Dunkelheit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dunkelheit.biz/tags/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Site Update October 2021</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/2021/site-update-october-2021.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/2021/site-update-october-2021.html</guid>
      <description>Henlo frens, this is a quick update to let you know what has changed with the site recently and what I plan to do going forward.
Recent Articles I have posted a few articles in the past week, I guess I was just in the mood for writing after almost a month of no updates.
The articles:
 2nd October 2021 - Stop Bloating Your Shell 27th September 2021 - The Emacs Rabbit Hole 24th September 2021 - Modern Books Suck  Books In the Modern Books Suck article I ranted about books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rewriting Some Posts</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/2021/rewriting-some-posts.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 19:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/2021/rewriting-some-posts.html</guid>
      <description>I am rewriting some of the posts on the site to be less ranty and more consistent with one another. I kinda rushed some of them so they look daft. I will update this post when the changes have been made.
Posts Updated:
 Free As In Freedom RSS Is Based Video Games Are Over What Does The Steam Deck Mean? - Removed due to being crap.  Here&amp;rsquo;s the summary of the Steam Deck post:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email and XMPP Available</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/2021/xmpp-available.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/2021/xmpp-available.html</guid>
      <description>XMPP chatting is now available.
You can contact me at w@dunkelheit.biz
Registration is not available at this time. I would recommend that you host your own XMPP service anyway.
You can learn how to host your own XMPP server at landchad.net or by watching this video by Mental Outlaw.
Update: Email is now available.
You can email me at w@dunkelheit.biz.
GPG information can be found on the contact page
There will be no registration or email hosting for strangers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching to Markdown Format</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/2021/switching-to-markdown-format.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/2021/switching-to-markdown-format.html</guid>
      <description>I am starting to get comfortable with hugo as a static site generator, I know I haven&amp;rsquo;t made my theme the &amp;ldquo;correct way&amp;rdquo; but for now it works to an acceptable minimum and most importantly the pages it produces are formatted perfectly.
I had an issue in that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t decide if I wanted to use Markdown or HTML when writing blog posts. The issue may seem silly (it is) but my reasons for having it were pretty straight forward:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
