<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2022 Archive on Dunkelheit</title>
    <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/2022/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2022 Archive on Dunkelheit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 17:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dunkelheit.biz/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who Cares About Twitter?</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/who-cares-about-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/who-cares-about-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Apparently it&amp;rsquo;s a big deal that Elon Musk bought Twitter. Everyone seems to be competing for the worst take regarding it. Which means it must be the Current Thing™️.
The true based and red pilled position is as always &amp;ldquo;who cares?&amp;rdquo;
Twitter sucks, it always sucked, it will continue to suck.
Elon Musk wants to &amp;ldquo;verify all humans&amp;rdquo;, this effectively means KYCAML for Twitter. Apparently his reasoning for buying Twitter is to secure free speech online or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encrypting an External Storage Device</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/encrypting-an-external-storage-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 09:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/encrypting-an-external-storage-device/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to keep backups of important data, it&amp;rsquo;s an even better idea to make sure only you can access them.
This is a guide on how to encrypt an external storage device for use on a Linux system.
Storage Devices This guide should be relatively universal for most external storage devices.
For this example I am assuming you know what kind of storage device is best for your use case and that you are using a NEW device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Update Jan/Feb 2022</title>
      <link>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/site-update-january-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunkelheit.biz/blog/site-update-january-2022/</guid>
      <description>January Update I made some changes to the site recently, they are as follows:
 Black outer page background ThinkPad grey background moved to inner region Border around inner page Removal of &amp;ldquo;UglyURLs&amp;rdquo; Restructured hierarchy  The site hierarchy was previously as follows:
/ -|blog/ -|2021/ -|post.html -|post2.html It is now following this hierarchy:
/ -|blog/ -|post -|post2 Additionally I changed some other minor details that aren&amp;rsquo;t worth mentioning specifically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
